Hello gas, we are going to talk about ICC
Lombard General Insurance. The results
of this company for the quarter ended 23 have been released.
How was the
result of this company and whether this company has
given dividend or not. We will
discuss this later, so definitely keep
watching the video till now. Talking about ICC Jalaun Bar General
Insurance, the
results of the company are presented in front of you.
All the amounts have been mentioned in the legs,
quarterly on a quarterly basis. We will
compare the results on a different basis. Right now, from
here, this is the result of this quarter.
This is the result of the previous quarter.
This is the result of the quarter from last year.
And this is the result of the full year 2023
and this is the result of 2022. Okay, if we
start with the income of the company from here, then the
cross premium income of the company from here,
net premium income, premium which is the
income here, after that there is interest. By
combining all these different types of income, the total income of the company can be seen in this quarter.
Above this, and from last year  Quarterly
comparison shows a rapid increase in the company's income.
Friends, on
top of this, the
company's income has been seen coming directly from 16 lakh to 18 lakh,
which is also a very
good thing. If we talk about the total expenses of this company, then the
brokerage cost of this company, net commission, and the cost of different
claims from here,
all these costs together give the total expense of the company of
3 lakh
97681 lakh. If you
go to see the quartering quadrant base, then the company's income is
big and the expenses of the company are
seen to be decreasing, which is another
very big
advantage for the company. If you go to see the performance of the company, then the
company's income is definitely
increasing rapidly here. Otherwise, the experience of the company is
not increasing that fast,
which is a very big positive
point. Okay, if we talk about the net profit of the company, then
after deducting taxes and express items, the net profit of the company is  The
profit is
seen to be 43696 lakhs which is on
quarter to quarter basis and the profit
of the company is seen to be increasing as compared to the quarter from last year,
otherwise friend, if you look at the performance of this company on Erode basis, then the
net profit of the company is ₹12701 lakhs in the
last year in 2022, which has increased to
₹17295 lakhs profit in this year 2023, okay, so the
result of the company is in this quadrant and
this year 2023 has a very good
result, according to me, this Dubai company has
given an out performance and keeping this result
in mind, there is a
good buying power from here in the coming time,
okay, otherwise if we
talk about the share on the earnings of this company, then brother, it has reached
around Rs 8.9, which is cold drink
water, above this and compared to the quarter from last year, it is
seen to be increasing
and above this also,
a good increase is seen in the share on the earnings of the company,
okay, rest  This company has
given its shareholders an advantage here by allowing its
shareholders to take a dividend of ₹550, the
record date of which has
not been mentioned by the company yet,
but the company will mention
its record date and ex-rate in the Annual General Meeting.
Along with this, the company has said that
within 30 days of the Annual General Meeting, this company will
pay its dividend in its bank account as per its schedule. So,
this company has achieved
very good results.
Along with achieving good results, the company has also
paid out a good dividend. So, this is a
huge advantage for communication. Keeping
this in mind, if you look at it, then
ICC Lombard General
Instruments is a good buying power in this communication.
First of all, if you are invested in this company, then the
first target will be Rs. 1000, the second
target will be Rs. 1290, after that.  The target will be 4
eight rupees and after that the medium term
target will be seen here around 1614.
Okay, so if you are
invested in ICC Lombard then
I would advise you to hold now.
You can expect a good rise in this market. Along with this, if
you are not invested in this market then
I will show you some levels where there are
mocks for buying. The first level to be
seen is the level of 1110 which can be
bought even at 120 rupees
and along with this it goes down. So the recent low
that the company had put is the level of ₹160,
above which the company will not come, still if it
comes then there is an opportunity to buy. Okay, so
this is our opinion about this company, that's all
for the truth. If you like the video then don't
forget to like and subscribe to the channel.
Good bye, good bye, see you again
in the next video.